aria.co.uk 2018-12-25

# Privacy Notice - Aria PC

## Who we are

We are Velo Systems Ltd hereinafter referred to as "Velo Systems","we", "us" or "our", the owners and operators of the Aria Retail and Gladiator Computers brands. Velo systems are committed to maintaining the trust and confidence of our customers, and we are not in the business of selling, renting or otherwise profiting from your personal information. The information which we hold on our customers is held purely for the purposes of providing a service as retailers of computers and computer components.

We may change and amend this Online Privacy Statement from time to time. So we recommend that you regularly access our website to ensure that you agree with any changes or amendments.

## Types of Data we collect

### Your personal details as required to complete your orders

In order to fulfill your purchase, we require your personal and contact details (Name(s), Email Address, Phone Numbers) and your Postal Address (for delivery and billing purposes). As outlined above, this information is only ever used by ourselves or shared with a third party for the specific purpose of providing you with your purchased goods or processing returns of those goods.

### Our Website Cookies

Our websites use cookies for the purposes of providing shopping basket functionality, and so as to gather information about browsing and purchasing behavior by our customers in order to improve our site.

### Google Analytics Cookies

When someone visits this website we use a third party service, Google Analytics, to collect standard Internet log information and details of visitor behavior patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. This information is only processed in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make, and do not allow Google to make, any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website.

### Mailing Lists

We maintain an opt-in mailing list for the purposes of email offer newsletters. To do this we use a third-party provider, MailChimp, to deliver our newsletters. We gather statistics around email opening and clicks using industry standard technologies which help us to monitor and improve our newsletters. For more information see MailChimp’s privacy notice.

We try to keep our email and telephone communication with our customers to the necessary minimum and only broadcast news and offers that are relevant and add value, if you no longer wish to receive emails from us you can find an unsubscribe link at the bottom of every marketing email we send; one click and your settings will immediately be updated.

### Other Cookies

This website includes third party widgets from partners which may create cookies in your browser. These include: 

  * Facebook and Twitter (for ‘like’, 'tweet' and ‘follow’ mechanisms)
  * Trustpilot (for the display of customer reviews)
  * PayPal, Amazon, Global Payments, V12 and BitPay (in order to accept payment through these payment agents)
  * Olark.com to provide a live chat service which allows website visitors to communicate directly with our sales and support teams.
  * Video.ly for embedded product-related videos on selected product details pages.

## Who your data will be shared with

Your personal data will only be shared with companies directly involved in the fulfillment of your orders from us. At no point do we sell or share your personal data to marketing agencies or to any business other than those directly involved in delivering to you the goods which you have purchased from us.

We use Royal Mail and DPD to deliver your orders. These companies will be provided with your name and delivery address in order to fulfill your order. DPD will additionally be provided with your mobile phone number (if you provided one) and your email address, so as to be able to keep you updated on the progress of your delivery.

## Security of your personal information

As a large and long-established online retailer, Velo Systems is part of the PCI (Payment Card Industry) compliance scheme. This means that our websites are regularly audited for security issues by ourselves and independently by third party accredited PCI compliance agencies.

In the event that there is ever a security breach which would allow unauthorised access to your personal information, Velo Systems undertakes to inform you promptly of the fact, such that you will be able to make informed decisions about whether you need to take action (e.g. changing passwords).

At no point do velo systems ever store or keep a permanent record of any of our customers’ payment details. Credit card numbers are never recorded for any purchase made through Velo Systems, whether online, on the phone, or in person. Payments are taken using well established industry-standard third-party payment agents (PayPal, Amazon, BitPay for bitcoin, Global Payments for card payments, and V12 Finance for financed payment).

All traffic to Velo Systems websites is encrypted using HTTPS (the industry standard protocol for the encryption of website traffic) protecting you from "online eavesdropping".

## Your access to your personal Information

Velo Systems is keen to ensure your privacy and protect your data, and respect the principles of data protection as outlined by the General Data Protection Regulation legislation which came into effect in May 2018.

For any requests relating to reviewing, correcting or removing the data we hold about you, please contact us using the contact details below. Velo Systems have put in place procedures for processing the privacy-related requests of our customers quickly and effectively according to the guidelines outlined in the GDPR.

In case the information we hold about you is outdated or incorrect you have the right to request an update and correction of the relevant data. You may also have a right to request the erasure of personal data we hold about you provided that we do not have a statutory obligation or an outweighing legitimate interest to keep such data.

## Contacting us for Privacy Requests

For any requests relating to your personal information please contact us at the address below:
